{
  "task": [
    {
      "question": "What did God call the firmament? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Earth"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Heaven"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Cloud "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Space "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. Heaven",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did God call the dry land and the waters? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Mountains; Oceans"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Valleys; Lakes"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Earth; Seas"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Stone; Water "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. Earth; Seas",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": "How did God create humans? ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. In His image"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Through evolution of primates"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. The goodness and love"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. The dust of the earth "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. In His image",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": "God command the following to Adam and Eve except?  ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Have dominion over all living things "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Work and be industrious"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Be fruitful and multiply"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Subdue the earth "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. Work and be industrious",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": "What God did on the seventh day?   ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Create children for the man and woman "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Rest"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Create wind "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Light "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. Rest",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": "God made the man out of ________?   ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Stone"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Dew"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. A piece of His own body "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Dust"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. Dust",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": " Where did God place His human creations?",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Garden"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Paradise"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Zion "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. The wilderness"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. Garden",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": "God create the woman out of _________? ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Dust "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Dew"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. From the rib of man"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Stone   "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. From the rib of man",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": " Why did God create  woman ________? ",
      "time": "10000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. So she could oversee the man"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. So she could keep the man company"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. So she could serve the man"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. So she could help the man"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. So she could help the man",
      "type": "epi_2"
    },
    {
      "question": " Who named the living creatures?  ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. God"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Adam & Eve"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Eve"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Adam"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. Adam",
      "type": "epi_2"
    }
  ]
}